Guide to the Consumer Reports. Colston E. Warne papers, 1910-1995 and undated RL.11784
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings, Speeches, Testimonies, 1922-1982 and undated; 9
  - Articles, 1924-1971 and undated; 7
    - 59. The High Cost of the Supermarket Revolution, 1967 (Box 117)
    - 60. Is It Time To Re-Evaluate the Consumer Activities of the Federal Government?, 1967 (Box 117)
    - 61. Private Versus Public Consumer Education, 1967 (Box 117)
    - 62. International Organization of Consumers Unions, 1970 (Box 117)
    - 63. The Impact of Consumerism on the Market, 1971 (Box 117)
    - 64. Who Will Control the Price Controllers?, 1971 (Box 117)
    - 65. How You Can Make Big Business Care About the Little Man, 1971 (Box 117)
    - 66. Protecting the Consumer, 1971 (Box 117)
    - 67. Consumer Affairs, 1971 (Box 117)
    - 68. Consumer Action Programs of Consumers Union of United States, 1971 (Box 117)
    - 69. The Consumer Revolt Against Business, undated (Box 117)
    - 70. Consumer Testing and Product Standardization, undated (Box 117)
    - 71. The Crisis in Reconversion, undated (Box 117)
    - 72. The Worldwide Consumer Movement, undated (Box 117)
  - Book Reviews`, 1929-1976 and undated; 8
    - 1. Cost of Living Studies, by Jessica B. Peixotto, 1929 (Box 117)
    - 2. A New Economic Order, by Kirby Page, 1930 (Box 117)
    - 3. Financing the Consumer, by Evans Clark, 1931 (Box 117)
    - 4. Labor Relations Under the Recovery Act, by Ordway Tead, 1933 (Box 117)
    - 5. Miners and Management, by Mary Van Kleeck, 1934 (Box 117)
    - 6. Merchandization in Industry, by Harry Jerome, 1934 (Box 117)
    - 7. Capitalism and Its Culture, by Jerome Davis, 1935 (Box 117)
    - 8. History and Labor in the United States, 1896-1932, Vol. III: Working Conditions, by Don D. Descohier, 1935 (Box 117)
    - 8a. Labor Legislation, by Elizabeth Brandeis, 1935 (Box 117)
    - 9. Rulers of America: A Study of Finance Capital, By Anna Rochester, 1936 (Box 117)
    - 10. English Cooperatives, by Sydney R. Elliott, 1938 (Box 117)
    - 11. The Consumer Cooperative as a Distributive Agency, by Orin E. Burley, 1939 (Box 117)
    - 12. The Nazi Economic System, by Otto Nathan, 1939 (Box 117)
    - 13. Harvard Cooperative Societv, Past and Present, by N.S.B. Gras, 1942 (Box 117)
    - 14. Consumer Installment Credit and Economic Fluctuations, by Gottfried Haberler, 1942 (Box 117)
    - 15. Consumer Problems in Wartime, edited by Kenneth Dameron, 1944 (Box 117)
    - 16. Economics for Consumers, by Leland Gordon, 1944 (Box 117)
    - 17. Witch Hunt: The Revival of Heresy, by Carey Williams, 1950 (Box 117)
    - 18. Meat and Man: A Study of Monopoly, Unionism, and Food Policy, by Lewis Corey, 1950 (Box 117)
    - 19. Men of Good Hope: A Study of American Progressives, by Daniel Aaron, 1951 (Box 117)
    - 20. The Cooperative Movement and Some of Its Problems, by Paul Hubert Casselman, 1952 (Box 117)
    - 21. Wartime Agriculture in Australia and New Zealand, 1939-1950, by J.G. Crawford, 1954 (Box 117)
    - 22. The Great Burlington Strike of 1888: A Case History in Labor Relations, 1956 (Box 117)
    - 23. Motivating Human Behavior, by Ernest Dichter, 1972 (Box 117)
    - 24. Citizen Nader, by Charles McCarry, 1972 (Box 117)
    - 25. Ralph Nader: A Man and a Movement, by Jay Acton and Alan Lemond, 1972 (Box 117)
    - 26. The Investigation of Ralph Nader: General Motors vs. One Determined Man, by Thomas Whiteside, 1972 (Box 117)
    - 27. Hit and Run: The Rise--And Fall? of Ralph Nader, by Ralph de Toledano, 1975 (Box 117)
    - 28. Nader's Support: Its Sources and Concerns, by Robert O. Herrmann and Rex H. Warland, 1975 (Box 117)
    - 29. Nader and the Power of Everyman, by Hays Gorey, 1975 (Box 117)
    - 30. Pretenders to the Throne, Chapter 5: Ralph Nader, Virtuoso of the Consumer Movement, by Lucy Black, 1976 (Box 117)
    - 31. Review of Nader book, undated (Box 117)
    - 32. Power Without Property, by Adolf A. Berle, undated (Box 117)
    - 33. Annotated bibliography, fragments, undated (Box 117)
  - Speeches, Talks, Lectures, 1929-1979 and undated; 9
    - 1. Quality Standards For Consumers' Cooperatives, Bryn Mawr College, 1929 (Box 117)
    - 2. The Close of the White Collar Era, Radio address, Rochester and Schenectady, 1930 (Box 117)
    - 3. The Consumer and the NRA League of Women Voters, Boston, 1933 (Box 117)
    - 4. An Appraisal of the New Deal, Continental Congress of Workers and Farmers, Boston, 1934 (Box 117)
    - 5. Can Capitalism Plan?, 1934 (Box 117)
    - 6. Taxation or Inflation, People's Lobby, 1935 (Box 117)
    - 7. Social Planning or Industrial Chaos? League for Industrial Democracy, 1937 (Box 117)
    - 8. The Challenge of the Consumer Movement, 1937 (Box 117)
    - 9. The Consumer and Modern Advertising, 1937 (Box 117)
    - 10. What are Minimum Essentials of Producer and Consumer Competency in Relation to the Sound Principles of Business Education? The Standpoint of an Economist, 1939 (Box 117)
    - 11. The Relation of the Consumer Movement to Scientific Groups, American Association of Scientific Workers, American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1939 (Box 117)
    - 12. Summary of speech on welfare economy, 1940 (Box 117)
    - 13. Is Advertising Now in the Public Interest? Wake Up America!, 1940 (Box 117)
    - 14. Address to American Association of Advertising Agencies, 1940 (Box 117)
    - 15. Transcript of meeting, part of above American Association of Advertising Agencies, 1940 (Box 117)
    - 16. Address by Donald E. Montgomery, in forum with Colston E. Warne, Fulton Oursler, and Stanley High, part of above American Association of Advertising Agencies, 1940 (Box 117)
    - 17. Speech at Advertising Club of Springfield, Statler Hotel, 1940 (Box 117)
    - 18. Consumer Education: A National Responsibility Institute for Consumer Education, 1941 (Box 117)
    - 19. The Consumer Looks At Advertising, Radio Address, CBS, 1941 (Box 117)
    - 20. Statement concerning CBS speech, 1941 (Box 117)
    - 21. A Rebel's Odyssey, Amherst College, 1941 (Box 117)
    - 22. A Consumer Program for Victory, 1942 (Box 117)
    - 23. Womanpower in Wartime, 1942 (Box 117)
    - 24. Government and Industry in War, People's Lobby, 1942 (Box 117)
    - 25. Talk at Springfield College, 1943 (Box 117)
    - 26. Should Advertising Be Drastically Curtailed in War-Time? Advertising Federation of America, Boston, 1943 (Box 117)
    - 27. The Scandal of War-Time Advertising, 1943 (Box 117)
    - 28. Is Washington Concerned With Consumers' Interests?, 1943 (Box 117)
    - 29. How Can America Strengthen the Council's Work?, 1943 (Box 117)
    - 30. What Organized Consumers Are Thinking, American Farm Bureau Association, 1943 (Box 117)
    - 31. The Place of the Consumer Movement, Second Annual Citizens Conference, Hamilton, NY, 1944 (Box 117)
    - 32. Consumer Education Through the Group Process, 1944 (Box 117)
    - 33. Government Control of Prices and Quality, People's Lobby, 1944 (Box 117)
    - 34. The Role of Consumer Testing in the Post War World, 22nd meeting of the National Industrial Conference Board, 1944 (Box 117)
    - 35. The Fighting Issue in Price Control Today, 1944 (Box 117)
    - 36. Public Ownership - When?, People's Lobby, 1945 (Box 117)
    - 37. Hypocrisy in War-Time Advertising, 1945 (Box 117)
    - 38. Advertising and the Paper Shortage, 1945 (Box 117)
    - 39. Needed: An Advertising Curfew - Let's Ration the Ads, 1945 (Box 117)
    - 40. Broadcast over ABC Network, Washington Story Hour, 1946 (Box 117)
    - 41. Consumers Organize, National Association of Consumers, 1946 (Box 117)
    - 42. Chapel Talk, Amherst College, 1947 (Box 117)
    - 43. Advertising - A Critic's Viewpoint, Advertising convention, Grand Rapids, Michigan, 1949 (Box 117)
    - 44. The Economic Consequences of the Cold War in the United States, Cultural and Scientific Congress for World Peace, 1949 (Box 117)
    - 45. A Consumer Looks At Advertising, First Detroit AFA Advertising Conference, 1949 (Box 117)
    - 46. Untitled, National Council for American-Soviet Friendship, 1949 (Box 117)
    - 47. Jobs in an Arms Economy, National Convention of the Young Progressives of America, 1949 (Box 117)
    - 48. Hope for the Consumer in 1949 (Box 117)
    - 49. What Peace and Freedom Mean to Education, Teachers Union Local 555, NYC, 1950 (Box 117)
    - 50. Consumer Clubs as a Technique for Lowering Costs and Stimulating Consumer Activity, 1950 (Box 117)
    - 51. How to Organize a Consumer Club, 1950 (Box 117)
    - 52. Are Price Controls Necessary?, 1951 (Box 117)
    - 53. Consumer Testing and Product Standardization, Kansas Home Economics Association, 1952 (Box 117)
    - 54. A Consumer's View of Advertising, Advertising Club of Hartford, 1952 (Box 117)
    - 55. Values in Insurance for the Consumer, Cooperative League of the USA, Insurance Conference, 1952 (Box 117)
    - 56. The Role of the Liberal Arts College, 1952 (Box 117)
    - 57. Resale Price Maintenance Should Be Abolished, 1952 (Box 117)
    - 58. The Role of the Consumer Movement, Harry M. Fife Memorial Lecture, Middlebury College, 1953 (Box 117)
    - 59. The Consumer and Television, Lord Jeff Club, Amherst College, 1954 (Box 117)
    - 60. Address, Semi-annual meeting of the New England group of the National Association of Educational Buyers, 1954 (Box 117)
    - 61. Getting Your Money's Worth - The Viewpoint of a Consumer Testing Agency, 1955 (Box 117)
    - 62. Civil Liberties, Springfield College, 1955 (Box 117)
    - 63. A Continuing Program of Consumer Education, Institute on Consumer Problems, University of Michigan, 1955 (Box 117)
    - 64. The Role of the Consumer Today, 1955 (Box 117)
    - 65. The Trade Unionist and Consumer Economics, 4th annual Union Leadership Training Institute, University of Kansas, 1956 (Box 117)
    - 66. Distribution - Pattern For Progress, Council of National Organizations, Atlantic City, New Jersey, 1956 (Box 117)
    - 67. The Consumer Looks At Foreign Consumer Programs, 1956 (Box 118)
    - 68. Remarks, National Consumer Credit Conference, 1956 (Box 118)
    - 69. How Backward is the Art of Spending Money?, Quality Control and the Consumer Conference, Rutgers University, 1957 (Box 118)
    - 70. How to Tell Consumers What They Want to Know, Advertising Club of New Jersey, 1957 (Box 118)
    - 71. Issues in the Uses of Consumer Credit, Institute on Consumer Credit Counseling Center, 1957 (Box 118)
    - 72. Credit Buying and Consumer Choice, Tenth Annual Industrial Relations Center Labor Conference, University of Michigan, 1958 (Box 118)
    - 73. Consumer Testing and Consumer Motivation, American Marketing Association, 1958 (Box 118)
    - 74. Advertising and Consumer Behavior, Mid-West Economics Association, Des Moines, Iowa, 1958 (Box 118)
    - 75. Packaging as a Technique of Deceit, 43rd National Conference on Weights and Measures, 1958 (Box 118)
    - 76. What Labor Can Gain From Association With the Consumer Movement, Conference on Unemployment and the Consumer, 1958 (Box 118)
    - 77. Outline of Topics for Discussion of Federal and State Food, Drug, and Cosmetic Laws and Their Enforcement, 62nd Annual Conference of the Association of the Food and Drug Officials of the United States, 1958 (Box 118)
    - 78. Food Standards, Consumers Union of United States, 1958 (Box 118)
    - 79. Debt Counseling is Key to Consumer Credit Competition, CUNA meeting, Washington, D.C., 1959 (Box 118)
    - 80. Consumer Quality, American Society for Quality Control, 1959 (Box 118)
    - 81. Management's Responsibility to the Consumer, Society for the Advancement of Management, University of Connecticut, 1959 (Box 118)
    - 82. Speech on patents, Annual Conference, Patent, Trademark, and Copyright Foundation of George Washington University, 1959 (Box 118)
    - 83. Safeguarding Labor's Dollar - What the Consumer Can Do, Fourth National Conference on Community Services, 1959 (Box 118)
    - 84. Why the Consumer Needs Protection, Conference Conference, University Extension, University of California, San Francisco, 1959 (Box 118)
    - 85. Consumers Union - Independent Guide to Family Shopping, New York State Federation of Women's Clubs, 1959 (Box 118)
    - 86. Progress Report on Consumer Organizations in Other Nations, New England Consumer Conference, Boston College, 1959 (Box 118)
    - 87. Quality Assurance for Home Products, American Society for Quality Control, Cleveland, 1959 (Box 118)
    - 88. Consumers Need Simpler Units, American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1959 (Box 118)
    - 89. A Continuing Program of Consumer Education, 1959 (Box 118)
    - 90. A Decisive Year for the Consumer, Consumer Concerns Conference, San Francisco, 1960 (Box 118)
    - 91. Advertising and Consumer Behvior, Ohio Association of Economists and Political Scientists, Oberlin College, 1960 (Box 118)
    - 92. New Fashions In Fraud, Consumer Problems and Prospects Conference, University of Texas, Austin, 1960 (Box 118)
    - 93. The Organized Consumer - His Impact on Marketing, American Marketing Association, Chicago, 1960 (Box 118)
    - 94. Consumer Testing - An Essential Tool in Consumer Education, Illinois Home Economics Association, 1960 (Box 118)
    - 95. The Influence of Ethical and Social Responsibilities on Advertising and Selling Practices, Allied Social Science Association, St. Louis, Missouri, 1960 (Box 118)
    - 96. Consumer Protection and Representation in Government: Problems, Progress, and Prospects, 1961 (Box 118)
    - 97. The Consumer, Victim of Planned Obsolescence, City Club, Cleveland, 1961 (Box 118)
    - 98. The Consumers Union, 1961 (Box 118)
    - 99. The Problem Appraised by a Consumer Spokesman, Ninth Annual Seminar in Marketing Management, Miami University, Oxford, Ohio, 1961 (Box 118)
    - 100. A Consumer's Look At Leisure, CU Conference, Sarah Lawrence College, 1961 (Box 118)
    - 101. Word of Greeting, Joint Conference on Vehical Design and Safety Research, 1961 (Box 118)
    - 102. Economic and Social Aspects of Advertising, Advertising Federation of America, 1961 (Box 118)
    - 103. The Independent Consumer Testing Agency - An International Answer to Brand Name Advertising, Tenth International Conference of the Green Meadow Foundation, Zurich, Switzerland, 1961 (Box 118)
    - 104. Deceptive Packaging - How It Fools You and What You Can Do About It, 1961 (Box 118)
    - 105. What Labor Can Gain From Association with the Consumer Movement, Conn. State Labor Council, Hartford, 1961 (Box 118)
    - 106. Advertising - Critic's View, Boston Conference on Distribution, 1961 (Box 118)
    - 107. Advertising, Brand Names and Price Behavior, Graduate Economics Society, Columbia University, 1961 (Box 118)
    - 108. The Challenge Facing Consumers - Home and Abroad, Morgan State College Conference, 1961 (Box 118)
    - 109. Tel Aviv Speech, 1962 (Box 118)
    - 110. Consumer Organizations Around the World, Eighth Annual Conference, Council on Consumer Information (American Council on Consumer Interests), Sarah Lawrence College, 1962 (Box 118)
    - 111. Consumer Protection in Government, Conference on Consumer Protection in California, San Francisco, 1962 (Box 118)
    - 112. A Hard Look At Contemporary Advertising Practices, Advertising and Sales Executives Club of Montreal, 1962 (Box 118)
    - 113. Chapel Talk, 1962 (Box 118)
    - 114. A Look At The Consumer Movement Today, Connecticut Home Economics Association, New London, Connecticut, 1962 (Box 118)
    - 115. Massachusetts Consumer Activity - Its Organization and Responsibility, Massachusetts Consumer Conference, Boston, 1962 (Box 118)
    - 116. Remarks, Third Annual Convention of the Association of California Consumers, San Francisco, 1962 (Box 118)
    - 117. Remarks, Meeting of the Massachusetts Advisory Consumer Council, 1962 (Box 118)
    - 118. International Office of Consumers Unions, Brussels, 1962 (Box 118)
    - 119. New Issues in Consumer Protection, Massachusetts State Federation of Women's Clubs, 1963 (Box 118)
    - 120. The Consumers' Stake in Standards, Thirteenth National Conference on Standards, 1963 (Box 118)
    - 121. What Can the Consumer Movement Do for Ameican Society?, Hanover Consumer Cooperative Society, 1963 (Box 118)
    - 122. Need Profitable Marketing Be at the Expense of the Consumer?, Marketing Association of Canada, Montreal, 1963 (Box 118)
    - 123. Protecting Consumer Interests, Co-Operative Education Guild, NYC, 1963 (Box 118)
    - 124. The Economic Impact of Advertising, Northampton High School, 1964 (Box 118)
    - 125. The Consumer Counts, Vermont Consumer Days, 1964 (Box 118)
    - 126. The American Marketing Revolution, Bryan Lectures in Financial Affairs, 1964 (Box 118)
    - 127. New Fashions In Deception, 1964 (Box 118)
    - 128. Planned and Unplanned Obsolescence, Bryan Lectures in Financial Affairs, 1964 (Box 118)
    - 129. The Changing Pattern of Consumer Responsibility, Bryan Lectures in Financial Affairs, 1964 (Box 118)
    - 130. The Dilemma of Modern Advertising, Bryan Lectures in Financial Affairs, 1964 (Box 118)
    - 131. Consumer Standards of Quality, Safety, and Product Performance, 1964 (Box 118)
    - 132. Consumer Sovereignty - Fact or Myth?, Chautauqua, NY, 1964 (Box 118)
    - 133. The Status of the Consumer in Our Economy, Past, Present, and Future, School of Home Economics, University of Missouri, 1965 (Box 118)
    - 134. Consumer Credit, A New Phenomenon, Tenth Annual AFL-CIO National Conference on Community Services, 1965 (Box 118)
    - 135. International Organization of Consumers Unions, 1965 (Box 118)
    - 136. Presentation, National Commission on Food Marketing, 1965 (Box 118)
    - 137. Consumer Protection, White House Conference on Health, 1965 (Box 118)
    - 138. Government Intervention and the Consumer, Association for Evolutionary Economics, NYC, 1965 (Box 118)
    - 139. Is It Time to Re-Evaluate the Consumer Protection Agencies Of The Government, Council on Consumer Information (American Council on Consumer Interests) Annual Conference, 1966 (Box 118)
    - 140. International Advertising and the Consumer Movement, 1966 (Box 118)
    - 141. Remarks, Fourth Biennial Conference, I.O.C.U., 1966 (Box 118)
    - 142. The Effects of Advertising on the Consumer, National Leadership Conference on Consumer Educatin and Financial Planning, 1966 (Box 118)
    - 143. Remarks, Consumers Union Thirtieth Anniversary Dinner, 1966 (Box 118)
    - 144. Consumer Education, A Re-Evaluation for a Supermarket Era, Iowa Home Economics Association, 1966 (Box 118)
    - 145. Marketing Implications of the World Consumer Movement, 1967 (Box 118)
    - 146. The American Consumer in 1967, University of Massachusetts (Box 118)
    - 147. Our International Responsibilities As Consumers, 20th Annual Meeting of the Consumers' Association of Canada, 1967 (Box 118)
    - 148. The Consumer Movement, A New and Significant Force in the American Economy, 71st Annual Conference of AFDOUS, 1967 (Box 118)
    - 149. Understanding Ourselves and the Market, Conference on Consumer Issues, Michigan State University, 1967 (Box 118)
    - 150. The Elderly as Consumers, Ninth Annual Conference, Indiana State Commission on the Aging, 1967 (Box 118)
    - 151. Money, Banking, and the Consumer, Eighth Annual Greater Hartford Forum, 1967 (Box 118)
    - 152. Health Information for the Consumer, National Health Council Conference, 1967 (Box 118)
    - 153. The Impact of Consumer Testing Organizations, American Society for Quality Control, New Haven, 1967 (Box 118)
    - 154. Advertising and the Consumer, Intercollegiate Business Game and Conference, Emory University, Atlanta, Georgia, 1968 (Box 118)
    - 155. Feedback From a Consumer Testing Organization, American Association for Quality Control, Philadelphia, 1968 (Box 118)
    - 156. The Consumer Front, Fifth Biennial Conference, I.O.C.U., 1968 (Box 118)
    - 157. Recent Developments in the Consumer Movement, Oregon Consumer League, Portland, 1968 (Box 118)
    - 158. Remarks on Self-Help, Consumer Assembly of Greater New York, 1969 (Box 118)
    - 159. A Rebel's Odyssey, 1969 (Box 118)
    - 160. The Consumer Looks at the Problem of Quality Hospital Care, Middle Atlantic Hospital Assembly, 1969 (Box 118)
    - 161. Automobile Insurance, The Consumer's Viewpoint, International of Insurance Council, 1969 (Box 119)
    - 162. A Consumer Approach to the Communications Problems of Developing Nations, First World Conference on Social Communication for Development, 1970 (Box 119)
    - 163. Consumer Interests in a New Decade: An Overview, American Council on Consumer Interests, 1970 (Box 119)
    - 164. Consumerism - A Menace to the Business Community?, Harvard Business School Club, 1970 (Box 119)
    - 165. Getting Good Value for the Hospital Food Dollar, 1970 (Box 119)
    - 166. Consumer Action Programs, 1970 (Box 119)
    - 167. Consumer Interests in the Decade of the Seventies, Sixth Biennial Conference, I.O.C.U., 1970 (Box 119)
    - 168. Consumers Look At Advertising, Advertising Age Workshop, 1970 (Box 119)
    - 169. The Role of Consumers Union in Protecting Consumers, American Marketing Association, 1970 (Box 119)
    - 170. Consumer Protection, 1970 (Box 119)
    - 171. A Consumer Organization Looks At Problems of Automobile Quality, American Society for Quality Control, 1970 (Box 119)
    - 172. Credible Consumer Communications, Public Relations Society of America, 1970 (Box 119)
    - 173. The Consumer Movement in World Development, Society for International Development, Canada, 1971 (Box 119)
    - 174. The New Consumerism - A Challenge to Home Economics Educational Association, 1971 (Box 119)
    - 175. Integrity for the Marketplace, Better Business Bureau of Eastern Massachusetts, 1971 (Box 119)
    - 176. The New Consumerism, Consumers Union, 1971 (Box 119)
    - 177. The Muted Voice of the Consumer in Regulatory Agencies, Institute of Public Utilities, 1971 (Box 119)
    - 178. Reflections on Jerome Hellerstein, Consumers Union, 1972 (Box 119)
    - 179. The Role of Consumer Testing Organizations in Maintaining Product Quality, American Society for Quality Control, 1972 (Box 119)
    - 180. Consumerism Today, 1972 (Box 119)
    - 181. Untitled, Consumer Federation of America, 1972 (Box 119)
    - 182. Advertising and the Consumer Movement, National Association of Accountants, 1973 (Box 119)
    - 183. The Elderly Consumer, American Association of Retired Persons, 1973 (Box 119)
    - 184. Remarks on Persia Campbell, Queens College, Flushing, NY, 1974 (Box 119)
    - 185. The Need for and Pathways to Consumer Education, 1974 (Box 119)
    - 186. Five Consumer Innovators of Yesteryear, Second National Symposium on the Consumer Movement, 1974 (Box 119)
    - 187. Address to CU Staff, Consumers Union, 1975 (Box 119)
    - 188. Hazards of the Credit System and Guarantee of Services, Ninth World Congress of Travel Agencies, 1975 (Box 119)
    - 189. Speech at Orangeburg, Consumers Union, 1975 (Box 119)
    - 190. The First Twenty Years of CU, 1936-1956, Part II, Address to CU Staff, 1976 (Box 119)
    - 191. Assessment of American Consumers, Consumers Union's 40th Anniversary, 1976 (Box 119)
    - 192. The Genesis of the Consumer Movement: The Ideological Roots of Consumerism, Colston E. Warne Lecture Series, Kansas State University, 1977 (Box 119)
    - 193. The Genesis of the Consumer Movement: The Launching of Consumers Union of United States, CEW Lecture Series, Kansas State University, 1977 (Box 119)
    - 194. The Proliferation of Consumer Organizations, Private and Public, CEW Lecture Series, Kansas State University, 1977 (Box 119)
    - 195. Lecture at Kansas State University, 1977 (Box 119)
    - 196. Advertising and the Consumer Movement, CEW Lecture Series, Kansas State University, 1977 (Box 119)